# **Newton Yan**

A passionate full stack web developer with 3 years of experience in creating high quality website and responsive web application. I have experience working with and have solid understanding in various web frameworks such as Angular and SvelteKit. Strong problem-solving skills and able to work collaboratively in a team environment. I'm eager to continue learning new technologies and adapting to new challenges.

yankaiyin@hotmail.com (647) 616-6144 www.newtonyan.com Toronto, ON, Canada

### **Education**

# The Chinese University of Hong Kong

**B.Eng in Systems Engineering and Engineering Management** | Sep 2015 – Nov 2019

- Second Class Upper Division
- Major GPA: 3.480/4.000

**Awards and Honors** 

- Outstanding Students Awards 2019
- The Professor Julie Hung Hsua Yu Scholarship for Intellectual Excel-leration
- The Yen Scholarship for Academic Excellence

### **Work Experience**

# **Belun Technology Company Limited**

Programmer Analyst | Sep 2021 – Apr 2023

- Analyzed user requirements and designed solutions that meet their needs
- Developed web applications with Ionic (Angular) and SvelteKit
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting for existing web applications
- Enhanced and maintained company website
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams by leveraging tools such as JIRA

# **Automated Systems (H.K.) Limited**

Analyst Programmer | Dec 2020 – Sep 2021

- Developed responsive web application with Vue.js
- Assisted in the development of the REST API using Spring Boot
- Collaborated with end-users to define application requirements

Programmer | Dec 2019 – Dec 2020

- Developed web application with Java and Apache Struts Framework
- Enhanced existing web application on .NET framework

# **Information Technology Services Centre, CUHK**

Student Helper | Jul 2018 – Jul 2019

• Designed multimedia courseware using Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects

## Language

Cantonese (Native)
English (Fluent)
Mandarin (Flutent)

### **Skills**

### (Advanced)

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

SvelteKit

Angular

Tailwind CSS

## (Intermediate)

React

Next.js

Express

MongoDB

MySQL

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe After Effects

#### Certificates

Professional Scrum Master II